W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Agencies, Boards, and Commissions, 1912-1980, undated; 1
  - Supreme Court, Judicial Procedures Reform Bill of 1937, Pamphlets and Reports (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court, Judicial Procedures Reform Bill of 1937, Pamphlets and Reports (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court, Petitions, Anti-Abortion, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Supreme Court, School Busing, Opinion Ballots, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Supreme Court, “The Third Branch,” Bulletins, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Tariff Commission, Correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Tariff Commission, Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Tariff Commission, Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (TVA), Correspondence, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - United Nations (UN), Correspondence and Literary Productions, 1945-1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Arm Control and Disarmament Agency, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - United States Railway Association, Press Releases, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Applications and Press Releases, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC), Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Clippings and Resolutions, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), “Congressional Record”, “Service Disabilities”, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence (1 of 2), 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence (2 of 2), 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Correspondence, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Dockets and Press Releases, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Fact Sheets and Resolutions, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Hospital Closings in Texas, Reports, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Pamphlet, “VA Benefits in Brief, 1964” (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Pamphlet, “VA in Texas”, 1956 July (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Pamphlets, 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Report, “1971 Fiscal Year Budget in Brief”, circa 1969 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Report of the Separation from Active Duty, Press Release, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), “Summary of Veterans’ Legislation Reported”, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Temple Contact Office, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Veterans and Survivors Pension Adjustment Act of 1974, Fact Sheet (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Veterans General Hospital Location, Correspondence and Resolutions, 1938-1940 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Waco Legal Division, Clippings and Printed Materials, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Waco Legal Division, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Waco Legal Division, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), Waco VA Regional Office, “Waco VA Quero Round-Up”, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Wage Stabilization Board, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - War Claims Commission, Correspondence, Forms, and Press Releases, 1950-1953 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - War Production Board, Uses for Cotton Burrs, Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Water Quality Association, Fact Sheet, 1978 January (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - World Bank, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Departments, 1916-1981, undated; 2
  Series II. Departments is by far the largest series in the collection. Materials in this series are divided according to the department of the executive branch to which they pertain. There are twelve subseries in total and are organized alphabetically: the Departments of Agriculture, Commerce, Defense, Energy, Health, Education, and Welfare, Housing and Urban Development, Interior, Justice, Labor, State, Transportation, and Treasury.
  The largest subseries in Series II is the Department of Agriculture, which reflects Bob Poage's legislative focus as a longtime member and brief chair of the House Committee on Agriculture.
  - Department of Agriculture, 1916-1981, undated; 1
    Subseries I consists of materials relating to the Department of Agriculture. This is one of the larger subseries in Series II. Departments, as Bob Poage was a long-time member of the House Committee on Agriculture and was a champion of agricultural issues.
    Several agencies feature prominently in the subseries including the Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, the Farmers Home Administration, the Office of the Secretary, and the Soil Conservation Service.
    Poage also collected significant runs of various bulletins produced by the Department of Agriculture including the “Farmers’ Bulletin” and the “Home and Garden Bulletin.”
    The materials in this subseries address a variety of topics including economic development, practical tips for farming, trade, raising livestock, crop insurance, and the Poage-Aiken Bill.
    The folders in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by agency or material type. Overall, the materials are in good condition.
    - Agricultural Extension, Correspondence and Tables, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - “Agricultural Supply & Demand Estimates”, Bulletin, 1978 January 26 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - “Agricultural Information Bulletin”, #99, “Conquest of the Land Through 7,000 Years”, 1953 August (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - “Agricultural Information Bulletin”, #345, “Assistance Available from the Soil Conservation Service”, 1970 October (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - “Agricultural Information Bulletin”, #371, “Home Freezing of Poultry and Poultry Main Dishes”, 1975 September (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Agricultural Research Service, Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Agricultural Research Service, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Agricultural Research Service, Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Agricultural Research Service, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Agricultural Research Service, Reports to Congress, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Research Service, W.O. Atwater Memorial Lectures, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Ag-Air Appeal, 1972-1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Clippings, Press Releases, and Printed Materials, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence and Statements, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Legal Complaint and Printed Materials, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, Printed Materials, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - American Leather Chemists Association, Journal Articles, 1944-1951 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service, Reports and Statements, 1974-1977 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Announcements, 1971-1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Announcements, 1976-1978 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Beltsville Agricultural Research Center, Report, 1974 August (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Blackland Experiment Station, Bulletins and Reports, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Blackland Experiment Station, Pamphlets and Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Blue Tongue, Correspondence and Leaflets, 1966-1968 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Booklet, “Packers and Stockyards Act, 1921, As Amended”, 1967 August (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Chemistry and Soils, Soil Survey, Falls County, Texas, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of Chemistry and Soils, Soil Survey, Williamson County, Texas, 1938 November (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of State Services Ad Hoc Committee, Minutes, 1965 November 19 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Central Texas Milk Orders, Correspondence and Dockets, 1954-1955 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights, Correspondence and Notice, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1974-1977 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Comments, Proposed Food Stamp Rules, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Agricultural Credit, Report, 1970 March (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Clipping and Summary, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Clippings, Printed Materials, and Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Clippings, Press Releases, and Statement, 1956-1958 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Clippings and Press Releases, 1965-1967 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Commodities Exchange, Memoranda and Summaries, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Press Releases and Reports, 1964, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Commodity Credit Corporation, Report of the President, 1976 September 30 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Drafts and Summaries, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Press Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Commodity Futures Trading Commission Act, Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Commodity Futures Trading Commission Act, Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Commodity Stabilization Service, Wyatt C. Hedrick, Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Coquat-Charollais Cattle, Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1950 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1950 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Fact Sheets, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1959 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1961 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1961 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1961 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1961 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1962 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1962 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1962 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1962 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1963 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1963 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1963 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1967 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1967 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Cotton Exports, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Cotton Insects Lab, Correspondence, 1969 January-February (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Cotton Research Laboratory, Brief, Austin, Texas, 1938 October 17 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Cotton Research Laboratory, Brief, Hillsboro, Texas, 1938 May (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Cotton Research Laboratory, “Preliminary Statement of a Cotton Research Program”, 1935 February (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Crop Insurance, Pamphlets and Statement, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Cropland Adjustment Program, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Democratic National Platform for Agriculture, Statements, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - “Directory of Federal Drought Assistance”, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Disinsection of Aircraft, Articles, 1961-1963 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Economic Cooperation Administration, Correspondence, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Executive Communications, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Executive Communications (1 of 2), 1955 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Executive Communications (2 of 2), 1955 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Executive Communications, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Executive Communications (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Executive Communications (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Executive Communications, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Executive Communications, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - “Fact Book of U.S. Agriculture”, 1976 March (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Fact Sheets for Part-Time Farmers and Gardeners, 1977, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1043, “Strawberry Varieties in the United States”, 1973 November (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1263, “Breeds of Swine”, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1537, “Johnsongrass as a Weed”, 1976 July (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1584, “Feedlot and Ranch Equipment for Beef Cattle”, 1976 October (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1869, “Foundations for Farm Buildings”, 1976 September (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1875, “Mushroom Growing in the United States”, 1977 March (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1889, “Fireplaces and Chimneys”, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1897, “Establishing and Managing Young Apple Orchards”, 1976 December (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #1972, “Poison Ivy, Poison Oak, and Poison Sumac”, 1977 August (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2035, “Making Land Produce Useful Wildlife”, 1975 February (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2088, “Infectious Anemia (Swamp Fever) of Horses, Mules, and Donkeys”, 1976 November (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2107, “Defense Against Radioactive Fallout on the Farm”, 1965 November (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2123, “Growing American Bunch Grapes”, 1977 December (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2125, “Making and Preserving Apple Cider”, 1977 January (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2126, “The Farm Beef Herd”, 1974 October (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2130, “Rope on the Farm”, 1973 January (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2136, “Lightning Protection for the Farm”, 1976 September (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2140, “Strawberry Diseases”, 1978 January (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2148, “Aphids on Leafy Vegetables”, 1977 May (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2161, “Your Farm Renting Problem”, 1977 February (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2164, “Your Farm Lease Contract”, 1976 September (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2167, “Family-Farm Records”, 1973 October (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2170, “Roofing Farm Buildings”, 1975 June (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2171, “How to Control a Gully”, 1973 June (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2179, “Father-Son Agreements for Operating Farms”, 1973 December (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2183, “Using Phenoxy Herbicides Effectively”, 1975 October (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2185, “Growing Cherries East of the Rocky Mountains”, 1977 November (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2193, “Grasshopper Control”, 1975 October (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2197, “Farm Poultry Management”, 1977 June (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2198, “Automatic Feeding Equipment for Livestock and Poultry”, 1977 March (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2199, “Forage and Cattle Management in Longleaf-Slash Pine Forests”, 1964 July (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2200, “Controlling Tomato Diseases”, 1976 December (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2202, “Simple Plumbing Repairs for the Home and Farmstead”, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2203, “Use of Concrete on the Farm”, 1976 September (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2206, “Foot Rot of Sheep”, 1972 March (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2211, “Controlling Dodder in Alfafa”, 1969 November (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2213, “Plumbing for the Home and Farmstead”, 1974 July (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2215, “Raising Ducks”, 1976 September (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2224, “Raising Livestock on Small Farms”, 1977 October (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2227, “Fire Restraint Construction: Of the HomeELOf Farm Buildings”, 1974 August (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2228, “Beef Cattle Breeds”, 1975 February (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2230, “Irrigated Pastures for Forage Production and Soil Conservation in the West”, 1975 September (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2234, “Ponds and Marshes for Wild Ducks on Farms and Ranches in the Northern Plains”, 1973 October (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2235, “Home Heating: Systems-Fuels-Controls”, 1977 November (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2237, “Water Supply Sources for the Farmstead and Rural Home”, 1977 December (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2240, “Preventing and Controlling Internal Parasites of Hogs”, 1977 December (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2243, “Farm Lighting”, 1976 May (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2245, “Sericea Lespedeza: Its Use and Management”, 1977 July (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2246, “Growing Strawberries in the Southeastern and Gulf Coast States”, 1977 March (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2247, “Fences for the Farm and Rural Home”, 1971 July (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2248, “Treating Farmstead and Rural Home Water Systems”, 1977 January (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2249, “Trout Ponds for Recreation”, 1976 July (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2250, “Warm-Water Fishponds”, 1977 April (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2251, “Raising Geese”, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2253, “What You Can Do About Bovine Mastitis”, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2255, “Identification and Control of Honey Bee Diseases”, 1977 May (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2256, “Building a Pond”, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 20)